[
    {
        "set_name": "sadas",
        "created_date": "2025-11-10 09:58:59",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "dasdas",
                "answer": "asd",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 2,
                    "times_wrong": 1
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "asd",
                "answer": "asdas",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 2,
                    "times_wrong": 1
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "as",
                "answer": "asds",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 2,
                    "times_wrong": 1
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "asd",
                "answer": "asd",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 2,
                    "times_wrong": 1
                }
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "set_name": "2131234",
        "created_date": "2025-11-10 18:42:11",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "sadasd",
                "answer": "12313"
            },
            {
                "question": "12",
                "answer": "123"
            },
            {
                "question": "213",
                "answer": "1231212"
            },
            {
                "question": "312",
                "answer": "312312"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "set_name": "as",
        "created_date": "2025-11-11 18:50:39",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "fwa",
                "answer": "aw",
                "custom_hint": "fwaf tite",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 8,
                    "times_wrong": 4
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "awdwad",
                "answer": "awd",
                "custom_hint": "asdsad tite",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 8,
                    "times_wrong": 4
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "awdwa",
                "answer": "awdaw",
                "custom_hint": "ass",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 7,
                    "times_wrong": 4
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "dwadwad",
                "answer": "sdfasd fsdfasf sd fsdfsdf sdf sdfsd",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 7,
                    "times_wrong": 4
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "as das as",
                "answer": "dasadasdas",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 7,
                    "times_wrong": 4
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "asdasd",
                "answer": "asda",
                "progress": {
                    "learned": false,
                    "times_correct": 6,
                    "times_wrong": 4
                }
            }
        ],
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "set_name": "dwa",
        "created_date": "2025-11-11 19:21:46",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "asdas",
                "answer": "asda"
            },
            {
                "question": "dwa",
                "answer": "dwa",
                "custom_hint": "ssss"
            },
            {
                "question": "dwa",
                "answer": "dwa"
            },
            {
                "question": "dwa",
                "answer": "daw"
            }
        ],
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "set_name": "10 Questions",
        "created_date": "2025-11-11 20:21:37",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "Question 1",
                "answer": "Answer 1"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 2",
                "answer": "Answer 2"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 3",
                "answer": "Answer 3"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 4",
                "answer": "Answer 4"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 5",
                "answer": "Answer 5"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 6",
                "answer": "Answer 6"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 7",
                "answer": "Answer 7"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 8",
                "answer": "Answer 8"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 9",
                "answer": "Answer 9"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 10",
                "answer": "Answer 10"
            }
        ],
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "set_name": "Sample",
        "created_date": "2025-11-11 20:21:48",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "Question 1",
                "answer": "Answer 1"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 2",
                "answer": "Answer 1"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 2",
                "answer": "Answer 1"
            },
            {
                "question": "Question 4",
                "answer": "Answer 1"
            }
        ],
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "set_name": "asdasdas",
        "created_date": "2025-11-11 20:21:58",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "asdasdas",
                "answer": "dasdasDASDA S"
            },
            {
                "question": "AS DFASDA SDAS",
                "answer": "dwdwdfwadwa awd awd asd asdfqeweD ASD"
            },
            {
                "question": "DAW DEAW",
                "answer": "D AWDAW DAW FESFAS FAS FAS A AS"
            },
            {
                "question": "GFAASDASD ASASFASF",
                "answer": "FAS FASFASA FASFASFASFASFAS A AS FAS F AS FASF ASF ASF AS AS FAS"
            }
        ],
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "set_name": "asdawd",
        "created_date": "2025-11-11 20:27:52",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "awawdawd",
                "answer": "awdawda"
            },
            {
                "question": "awdawd",
                "answer": "awdwa"
            },
            {
                "question": "dwad",
                "answer": "awdwa"
            },
            {
                "question": "dwa",
                "answer": "dwadwawa"
            }
        ],
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    }
]